✔ capacity, common scramble, prepared handshake and start epoch (2.1591ms)
✔ finish before GO rejected; duplicates cannot rewrite time (0.435ms)
✔ receipt timestamps determine winner despite reversed function order (0.2701ms)
✔ tie, timeout and disconnect grace (0.2934ms)
✔ both must agree to rematch and stale commands cannot affect next round (0.3416ms)
✔ leave before GO resets readiness and host; final departure deletes room (0.2093ms)
✔ scramble excludes adjacent moves on the same axis (2.4285ms)
✔ shared notation gives identical cubes and inverse solves them (13.8433ms)
✔ four x/-1 turns and inverse retain cubies/stickers (9.4988ms)
✔ four x/0 turns and inverse retain cubies/stickers (2.3203ms)
✔ four x/1 turns and inverse retain cubies/stickers (1.9666ms)
✔ four y/-1 turns and inverse retain cubies/stickers (2.2185ms)
✔ four y/0 turns and inverse retain cubies/stickers (2.3134ms)
✔ four y/1 turns and inverse retain cubies/stickers (1.69ms)
✔ four z/-1 turns and inverse retain cubies/stickers (1.5278ms)
✔ four z/0 turns and inverse retain cubies/stickers (1.4055ms)
✔ four z/1 turns and inverse retain cubies/stickers (0.88ms)
✔ 100 mixed moves and their reverse have no drift or sticker loss (11.7175ms)
✔ raycast/swipe chooses all axes from both sides and orbited viewpoints (7.1031ms)
✔ a narrow seam selects a cubie, but a drag outside the cube stays outside (1.6152ms)
✔ pointer ownership, tap/cancel, one turn per swipe, then idle and dispose (7.5881ms)
✔ pause while animating snaps atomically and resume has no pending gesture (2.4244ms)
✔ undo reverses successive swipes; reset restores solved cube and camera (4.8254ms)
ℹ tests 23
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 23
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 197.6823
